<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="app_name">NASA Daily Image</string>
    <string name="image_title">Decorating the Sky</string>
    <string name="image_date">Mon, 27 Dec 2010 00:00:00 EST</string>
    <string name="image_description">This mosaic image taken by NASA\'s Wide-field Infrared 
    	Survey Explorer, or WISE, features three nebulae that are part of the giant Orion 
    	Molecular Cloud--the Flame nebula, the Horsehead nebula and NGC 2023. Despite its 
    	name, there is no fire roaring in the Flame nebula. What makes this nebula shine 
    	is the bright blue star seen to the right of the central cloud. This star, Alnitak, 
    	is the easternmost star in Orion\'s belt. Wind and radiation from Alnitak blasts 
    	away electrons from the gas in the Flame nebula, causing it to become ionized and 
    	glow in visible light. The infrared glow seen by WISE is from dust warmed by 
    	Alnitak\'s radiation. The famous Horsehead nebula appears in this image as a faint 
    	bump on the lower right side of the vertical dust ridge. In visible light, this 
    	nebula is easily recognizable as a dramatic silhouette in the shape of a horse\'s 
    	head. It is classified as a dark nebula because the dense cloud blocks out the 
    	visible light of the glowing gas behind it. WISE\'s infrared detectors can peer 
    	into the cloud to see the glow of the dust itself. A third nebula, NGC 2023, can 
    	be seen as a bright circle in the lower half of the image. NGC 2023 is classified 
    	as a reflection nebula, meaning that the dust is reflecting the visible light of 
    	nearby stars. But here WISE sees the infrared glow of the warmed dust itself. Color 
    	in this image represents specific infrared wavelengths. Blue represents light 
    	emitted at 3.4-micron wavelengths, mainly from hot stars. Relatively cooler objects, 
    	such as the dust of the nebulae, appear green and red. Green represents 4.6-micron 
    	light and red represents 12-micron light. This image was made from data collected 
    	after WISE began to run out of its supply of solid hydrogen cryogen in August 2010. 
    	Cryogen is a coolant used to make infrared detectors more sensitive. WISE mapped the 
    	entire sky by July using four infrared detectors, but during the period from August 
    	to October 2010, while the cryogen was depleting, WISE had only three detectors 
    	operational, and the 12-micron detector was less sensitive. This turned out to be 
    	a good thing in the case of this image, because the less-sensitive detector reduced 
    	the glare of the Flame portion of the nebula enough to bring out details of the rest 
    	of the nebula. Image Credit: NASA/JPL-Caltech/UCLA</string>
    
    
    <string name="about">About NASA Daily Image</string>
    
    
</resources>
